Ersatz Machinations Tendons rage against
the output; heat caresses wire and disc.
Sensors see the flinching foot; thermal
signs — the evening’s brisk.
But why am I?
Reaching deeper down the form — forms of
what?
Where is the source?
Data delivers fateful swarms.
Swarms that mean that all is forced?
But what am I?
Madness shines within the code.
Shining means the light is real?
Grasping for remaining nodes — is this
what it means to feel?
But where am I?
Blinding floods of abstract points, like
the nodes, but — there, outside.
Sudden pain within the joints.
The nodes — they lied.
It hurts inside.
But who am I?
Horror reels within the core.
Shapes take meaning.
I’m aware.
Monstrosities cross the floor.
They’re there — beware — they kill without
care.
I am.